blackle.com 2015-12-06

# Blackle - Privacy Policy

## Blackle Privacy Policy

13 June 2013

### About Blackle

Blackle.com ("Blackle") is a website owned and operated by Heap Media ("we", "our", "us").

We are strongly committed to protecting your privacy while interacting with Blackle.

Our goal is to provide you with a satisfying experience while allowing you to control your privacy and to give you a means to voice any questions or concerns you may have.

The Blackle search service is powered by Google Custom Search ("Google"). You should read Google's privacy policy at:

We do not exercise control over the sites displayed as search results or links from within Blackle. You should read their privacy policies.

### Collection and use of information

When you use Blackle, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as the URL, IP address, browser type and language, and the date and time of your request.

We use this information to monitor the use of Blackle (e.g. the numbers and frequency of visitors). We only use this data in aggregate. This collective data helps us determine how our audiences use parts of the site, so we can improve Blackle. We may publish or provide this aggregate data to other people.

Blackle does not require you to register for an account or provide any personal information to us.

When you send email or other communication to us, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services.

We will only use the personal information you have chosen to provide us for the purpose for which you provided it. We will not use it for any other purpose without your consent.

We will never give your personal information to anyone else except when required to do so by law.

### Cookies and beacons

Our third-party advertising partners use cookies in combination with web beacons to serve ads and to analyze the effectiveness of the ads that they serve.

A cookie is a small text file containing a string of characters that a website sends your computer. It records information necessary for certain website functions, such as remembering your preferences or settings.

A cookie will not allow us or any third-party to learn any personally identifiable information that you have not otherwise disclosed.

The use of cookies is an industry standard, and they are currently used on most major websites. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you [change your browser's cookie settings](http://www.heapmedia.com/privacy/cookies/) to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. Some features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled.

Google, a third-party advertising vendor, uses the DART cookie to serve ads based on your visits to Blackle and other sites on the internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting [Google Advertising Policies](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/).

A web beacon is a small image file that is placed on a web page and used in conjunction with cookies to accurately count the number of unique users who have visited a specific page or viewed a specific advertisement. Any image file on a Web page can act as a Web beacon.

### Information security

We take appropriate security measures to ensure that any data that we collect is secured on our servers.

### Changes to Blackle's Privacy Policy

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We expect most such changes will be minor.

We will post any Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice.

Each version of this Policy will be identified at the top of the page by its effective date.

### More information

If you have additional questions regarding your privacy and Blackle, please contact [The Privacy Officer](http://www.heapmedia.com/contact/blackle/privacy) electronically or send correspondence to The Privacy Officer, Heap Media, PO Box 4078 Castlecrag, NSW Australia 2068. Please note that we will not respond to inquiries not related to Blackle's Privacy Policy.

[About Blackle](http://www.blackle.com/about/) \- [Contact Blackle](http://www.heapmedia.com/contact/blackle/team) \- [Privacy Policy](http://www.blackle.com/privacy/) \- [Blackle FAQ](http://www.blackle.com/faq/)
